giveaway-club.com 2016-12-02

# Privacy Policy

## 1\. Sites and products covered by this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all Auslogics Labs Pty Ltd ("Auslogics") owned websites and domains ("Auslogics Websites") and all software products developed and published by Auslogics (“Auslogics Products”). Auslogics Websites (including giveaway-club.com) and Auslogics Products may provide links to third-party websites and products. If you access those links or install and use those products, that interaction will not be covered by this Privacy Policy, as Auslogics has no control over third-party websites, products and their policies. Auslogics specifically disclaims any and all liability, in contract or in tort, arising from your use of any link to any third-party website, or your use of any third-party product. The personal data you choose to give to unrelated third parties is not covered by the Auslogics Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information. Some third-party companies may choose to share their personal data with Auslogics; that sharing is governed by that third-party company's privacy policy.

## 2\. Types of information we collect

This Privacy Policy covers personal information, non-personal data collection and aggregate reporting. Personal information is information that is associated with your name or personal identity. Auslogics uses personal information to deliver products and provide you with better service. Once you choose to provide us with personal information, you can be assured it will be used only to support your customer relationship with Auslogics. We take seriously the trust you place in us. Auslogics will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others. Non-personal information is data about usage and service operation that is not associated with a specific personal identity. Auslogics collects and analyzes non-personal information to evaluate how visitors use the Auslogics Websites or how users interact with Auslogics Products. Non-personal data we collect may include the pages visited on the Auslogics Websites, unique URLs visited within giveaway-club.com, browser type and IP address. Most non-personal data is collected via cookies or other analysis technologies. Auslogics web pages use cookies and other technologies for data analysis and personalization services. 

## 3\. How we use your information

Auslogics uses your personal information to provide you with services and to help us better understand your needs and interests. Non-personal data is aggregated for reporting about Auslogics websites usability, performance and effectiveness. It is used to improve the customer experience, usability and site content. By using an Auslogics website or websites, you consent to the collection, use and/or dissemination of information about you according to the terms stated herein.

## 4\. Who we share your information with

Auslogics will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others. Auslogics shares customer information with companies working on our behalf, but only as described above in "How we use your information." Auslogics will not share personal information with any other third parties without your permission, unless required by law enforcement action, subpoena, or local law.

## 5\. Keeping your information secure

Auslogics is committed to protecting the information you provide us. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, Auslogics has in place appropriate physical and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect.
